ILR School Extension Division (Buffalo, N.Y.) Nellie Brown Files /4283/002
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Blood Borne Pathogens/Confined Space/Ergonomics- Erie County, 2010 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  WNYCOSH, #3842, 10/12/10
- Blood Borne Pathogens/Confined Space/Ergonomics- Erie County, 2010 (Box 31, Folder 14)
  WNYCOSH, #3843, 10/14/10
- Blood Borne Pathogens/Confined Space/Ergonomics- Erie County, 2010 (Box 31, Folder 15)
  WNYCOSH, #3844, 11/16/10
- Blood Borne Pathogens/Confined Space/Ergonomics- Erie County, 2010 (Box 31, Folder 16)
  WNYCOSH, #3845, 11/18/10
- Tech. Asst., 2010 (Box 31, Folder 17)
  SUCAB, #3846, 11/03/10
- Shiftwork, 2011 (Box 31, Folder 18)
  NYWEA, #3847, 2/8/11
- Confined Space, 2010 (Box 31, Folder 19)
  WNYCOSH, #3848, 10/16/10
- Niagara Falls, 2010 (Box 31, Folder 20)
  WNYCOSH, #3849, 9/23/10
- N.F. Violence [Folders 1-15], 2010 (Box 31, Folder 21)
  WNYCOSH, #3850-3864, 9/23/10-11/17/10
- Noise, 2010 (Box 31, Folder 22)
  #3865
- Tech. Asst. (Proposed), 2010 (Box 31, Folder 23)
  NYSCOPBA, #3866
- Work, Health, Health Care, 2011 (Box 31, Folder 24)
  Cornell ILR Res., #3867, 2/15/11
- Tech. Asst., 2010 (Box 31, Folder 25)
  #3868
- Indoor Air Quality, 2010 (Box 31, Folder 26)
  #3869
- Chemicals, 2010 (Box 31, Folder 27)
  #3870
- Job Hazard Analysis for Composting, 2011 (Box 31, Folder 28)
  US Composting Council, #3871, 1/24/11
- How You Can Recover, 2011 (Box 31, Folder 29)
  US Composting Council, #3872, 1/24/11
- Tech. Asst., 2010 (Box 31, Folder 30)
  #3873, 9/3/10
- LRRP-I (Proposal), 2010 (Box 31, Folder 31)
  Broome County Dept. of Health, #3874
- City/Buffalo Schools, 2010 (Box 31, Folder 32)
  WNYCOSH, #3877, 10/18/10
- City/Buffalo Schools, 2010 (Box 31, Folder 33)
  WNYCOSH, #3878, 10/19/10
- Buffalo Schools, 2010 (Box 31, Folder 34)
  WNYCOSH, #3879, 10/19/10
- Buffalo Schools, 2010 (Box 31, Folder 35)
  WNYCOSH, #3880, 10/21/10
- Buffalo Schools, 2010 (Box 31, Folder 36)
  WNYCOSH, #3881, 10/22/10
- Buffalo Schools, 2010 (Box 31, Folder 37)
  WNYCOSH, #3882, 10/26/10
- Buffalo Schools, 2010 (Box 31, Folder 38)
  WNYCOSH, #3883, 10/26/10
- Buffalo Schools, 2010 (Box 31, Folder 39)
  WNYCOSH, #3884, 10/27/10
- Buffalo Schools, 2010 (Box 31, Folder 40)
  WNYCOSH, #3885, 10/28/10
- Buffalo Schools, 2010 (Box 31, Folder 41)
  WNYCOSH, #3886, 10/29/10
- Buffalo Schools, 2010 (Box 31, Folder 42)
  WNYCOSH, #3887, 11/1/10
- Buffalo Schools, 2010 (Box 31, Folder 43)
  WNYCOSH, #3888, 11/1/10
- Lead Worker (Proposed), 2010 (Box 31, Folder 44)
  Chautauqua County Rehab., #3889
- Hazmat-R, 2011 (Box 31, Folder 45)
  IUOE, #3891, 2/1/11
- Hazmat-R, 2011 (Box 31, Folder 46)
  IUOE, #3892, 2/2/11
- Hazmat-R, 2011 (Box 31, Folder 47)
  IUOE, #3890, 1/31/11
- Hazmat-R, 2011 (Box 31, Folder 48)
  IUOE, #3893, 2/3/11
- Hazmat-R, 2011 (Box 31, Folder 49)
  IUOE, #3894, 2/4/11
- Mold, 2010 (Box 31, Folder 50)
  MRB, #3895, 11/8/10
- Chemicals, 2010 (Box 31, Folder 51)
  MRB, #3896, 11/8/10
- Hazmat-I, 2011 (Box 31, Folder 52)
  IUOE, #3897, 2/17/11
- N.F.- Violence, 2010 (Box 31, Folder 53)
  WNYCOSH, #3898, 11/17/10
- N.F.- Violence, 2010 (Box 31, Folder 54)
  WNYCOSH, #3899, 11/19/10
- N.F.- Violence, 2010 (Box 31, Folder 55)
  WNYCOSH, #3900, 11/19/10
- Lead Renovator Initial, 2011 (Box 31, Folder 56)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 10C#3901, 1/11/11, Brown/Wheaton
- Lead Renovator Initial, 2011 (Box 31, Folder 57)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 10C#3902, 1/12/11, Brown/Wheaton
- Lead Renovator Initial, 2011 (Box 31, Folder 58)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, #3903, 3/2/11, Wheaton
- Lead Renovator Initial, 2011 (Box 31, Folder 59)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, #3904, 3/3/11, Wheaton
- Lead Renovator Initial, 2011 (Box 31, Folder 60)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, #3905, 2/1/11, Wheaton
- Lead Renovator Initial, 2011 (Box 31, Folder 61)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, #3906, 2/2/11, Wheaton
- Lead Renovator Initial, 2011 (Box 31, Folder 62)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, #3907, 2/15/11, Wheaton
- Lead Renovator Initial, 2011 (Box 31, Folder 63)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, #3908, 2/16/11, Wheaton
- Lead Renovator Initial, 2011 (Box 31, Folder 64)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, #3809, 3/8/11, Wheaton
- Lead Renovator Initial, 2011 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, #3910, 3/9/11, Wheaton
- Lead Renovator Initial, 2011 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, #3911, 3/15/11, Wheaton
- Lead Renovator Initial, 2011 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, #3912, 3/16/11, Wheaton
- Lead Renovator Initial, 2011 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, #3913, 4/12/11, Wheaton
- Lead Renovator Initial, 2011 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, #3914, 4/13/11, Wheaton
- Lead Renovator Initial, 2011 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, #3915, 4/26/11, Wheaton
- Lead Renovator Initial, 2011 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, #3916, 4/27/11, Wheaton
- Lead Renovator Initial, 2011 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 10C#3917, 5/10/11, Brown/Wheaton
- Lead Renovator Initial, 2011 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 10C#3918, 5/11/11, Brown/Wheaton
- Lead Renovator Initial, 2011 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 10C#3919, 5/24/11, Brown/Wheaton
- Lead Renovator Initial, 2011 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 10C#3920, 5/25/11, Brown/Wheaton
- Lead Renovator Initial, 2011 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 10C#3921, 6/7/11, Brown/Wheaton
- Lead Renovator Initial, 2011 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 10C#3922, 6/8/11, Brown/Wheaton
- Lead Renovator Initial, 2011 (Box 32, Folder 14)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 10C#3923, 6/14/11, Brown/Wheaton
- Lead Renovator Initial, 2011 (Box 32, Folder 15)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 10C#3924, 6/15/11, Brown/Wheaton
- Lead Renovator Initial, 2011 (Box 32, Folder 16)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, #3928, 7/20/11, Wheaton
- Lead Renovator Initial, 2011 (Box 32, Folder 17)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, #3927, 7/19/11, Wheaton
- Lead Renovator Initial, 2011 (Box 32, Folder 18)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, #3926, 7/13/11, Wheaton
- Lead Renovator Initial, 2011 (Box 32, Folder 19)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, #3925, 3/12/11, Wheaton
- Lead Renovator Initial, 2011 (Box 32, Folder 20)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, #3929, 8/9/11, Wheaton
- Lead Renovator Initial, 2011 (Box 32, Folder 21)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, #3930, 8/10/11, Wheaton
- Lead Renovator Initial, 2011 (Box 32, Folder 22)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, #3931, 8/30/11, Wheaton
- Lead Renovator Initial, 2011 (Box 32, Folder 23)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, #3932, 8/31/11, Wheaton
- Lead Renovator Initial, 2011 (Box 32, Folder 24)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, #3933, 9/13/11, Wheaton
- Lead Renovator Initial, 2011 (Box 32, Folder 25)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, #3934, 9/14/11, Wheaton
- Lead Renovator Initial, 2011 (Box 32, Folder 26)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, #3935, 9/26/11, Wheaton
- Lead Renovator Initial, 2011 (Box 32, Folder 27)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, #3936, 9/27/11, Wheaton
- Lead Renovator Initial, 2011 (Box 32, Folder 28)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, #3937, 10/5/11, Wheaton
- Lead Renovator Initial, 2011 (Box 32, Folder 29)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, #3938, 10/18/11, Wheaton
- Lead Renovator Initial, 2011 (Box 32, Folder 30)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, #3939, 11/1/11, Wheaton
- Lead Renovator Initial, 2011 (Box 32, Folder 31)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, #3940, 11/15/11, Wheaton
- Lead Renovator Initial, 2011 (Box 32, Folder 32)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, #3941, 12/6/11, Wheaton
- Lead Renovator Initial, 2011 (Box 32, Folder 33)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, #3942, 12/20/11, Wheaton
- No. 3943: Monroe County Water Authority [Folder 1 of 3], 2009-2010 (Box 32, Folder 34)
- No. 3943: Monroe County Water Authority [Folder 2 of 3], 2009-2010 (Box 32, Folder 35)
- No. 3943: Monroe County Water Authority [Folder 3 of 3], 2009-2010 (Box 32, Folder 36)
- Disaster Worker, 2011 (Box 32, Folder 37)
  IUOE, #3944, 2/21/11
- Disaster Worker, 2011 (Box 32, Folder 38)
  IUOE, #3945, 2/24/11
- Disaster Worker, 2011 (Box 32, Folder 39)
  IUOE, #3946, 2/23/11
- Content that Works, 2010 (Box 32, Folder 40)
  #3947
- Composting Hazards, 2011 (Box 32, Folder 41)
  CAL Recycle, #3948, 1/26/11
- No. 3949: Gowanda Nursing Home [Folder 1 of 2], 2010-2011 (Box 32, Folder 42)
- No. 3949: Gowanda Nursing Home [Folder 2 of 2], 2010-2011 (Box 32, Folder 43)
- Lab Safety, 2011 (Box 32, Folder 44)
  WNYCOSH, #3950, 5/3/11
- Cancer and Environment, 2011 (Box 32, Folder 45)
  NYSUT, #3951, 3/5/11
- Green Cleaning, 2011 (Box 32, Folder 46)
  WNY Environment Summit, #3952, 9/24/11
- Buffalo S.D.- Food Service, 2011 (Box 32, Folder 47)
  WNYCOSH, #3953, 1/12/11
- Article, 2011 (Box 32, Folder 48)
  Women, #3955, 1/17/11
- Buffalo School District- Food Service, 2011 (Box 32, Folder 49)
  WNYCOSH, #3954, 1/12/11
- MI and Learning Science, 2010 (Box 32, Folder 50)
  Clarence HS Chem Dept., #3956, 12/17/10
- Violence, 2011 (Box 32, Folder 51)
  NYWEA, #3957, 2/8/11
- LRRP- I, 2010 (Box 32, Folder 52)
  MRB Construction, #3960, 12/21/10
- Conference- Critters, 2011 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  CSEA, #3961, 4/9/11
- IUOE, 2010-2011 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  NYSDOL HAB
- IUOE, 2011-2012 (Box 33, Folder 3)
- JHA- ITT STD, 2010 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  WNYCOSH, #3962, 12/16/10
- Buffalo School District- Food Service- Hazcom, 2011 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  WNYCOSH, #3963, 3/16/11
- Buffalo School District- Food Service- Integrated Pest Mgmt., 2011 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  WNYCOSH, #3964, 3/16/11
- NFWB- Violence, 2011 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  WNYCOSH, #3965, 5/16/11
- NFWB- Violence, 2011 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  WNYCOSH, #3966, 5/16/11
- NFWB- Violence, 2011 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  WNYCOSH, #3967, 5/25/11
- Brooks Hospital- Violence, 2011 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  WNYCOSH, #3968, 1/19/11
- Violence- Brooks Hospital, 2011 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  WNYCOSH, #3969, 2/10/11
- Brooks Hospital- Violence, 2011 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  WNYCOSH, #3970, 3/14/11
- Workplace Violence Prevention, 2011 (Box 33, Folder 13)
  WNYCOSH, #3971
- Tech. Asst., 2010 (Box 33, Folder 14)
  NYS Attorney General, #3972, 11/29/10
- Training (Proposal), 2010 (Box 33, Folder 15)
  MRB Inc., #3973
- Work, Health, and Health Care, 2011 (Box 33, Folder 16)
  Cornell Resident/Ext., #3974
- Tech. Asst., 2010 (Box 33, Folder 17)
  #3975, 12/06/10
- Confined Space- Manure Storage, 2011 (Box 33, Folder 18)
  WNYCOSH, #3976, 1/18/11
- Tech. Asst., 2011 (Box 33, Folder 19)
  Cornell Manure Mgmt., #3977, 1/3/11
- Mold- MRB, 2011 (Box 33, Folder 20)
  WNYCOSH, #3978, 2/22/11
- Chemical Safety- MRB, 2011 (Box 33, Folder 21)
  WNYCOSH, #3979, 2/22/11
- LRRP- I, 2011 (Box 33, Folder 22)
  MRB Construction, #3980, 1/27/11
- Tech. Asst., 2011 (Box 33, Folder 23)
  MCWA, #3981, 1/13/11
- AFL-CIO Meeting, Global Harmonization, 2011 (Box 33, Folder 24)
  WNYCOSH, #3982, 6/14/11
- Tech. Asst.- JHA/Ergo., 2011 (Box 33, Folder 25)
  Brooks Hosp., #3983, 5/5/11
- ITT STD- Accident Investigation, 2011 (Box 33, Folder 26)
  WNYCOSH, #3984, 4/5/11
- Lead and Mold Training (Proposed), 2011 (Box 33, Folder 27)
  ECC, #3985
- Violence Prevention- ECWA, 2011 (Box 33, Folder 28)
  Henderson Woods, #3986
- Lead Worker Initial, 2011 (Box 33, Folder 29)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 11C#3987, 11/28-29/11, Balfour
- Tech. Asst., 2011 (Box 33, Folder 30)
  University of Arizona, #3988, 3/31/11
- Article, 2011 (Box 33, Folder 31)
  #3989
- Lead Hotline for Erie County, 2011 (Box 33, Folder 32)
  Apollo Alliance, #3990, 4/2011-
- Workplace Violence Prevention, 2011 (Box 33, Folder 33)
  WNYCOSH, #3991
- NFWB- Violence, 2011 (Box 33, Folder 34)
  WNYCOSH, #3992, 6/7/11
- NYSTA, 2011 (Box 33, Folder 35)
  WNYCOSH, #3993, 4/26/11
- Reviewer for M.O.P. #1, 2011 (Box 33, Folder 36)
  W.E.F., #3994, 5/2/11
- No. 3995: Precarious Workers: Nail Technicians [Folder 1 of 4], 2011 (Box 33, Folder 37)
- No. 3995: Precarious Workers: Nail Technicians [Folder 2 of 4], 2011 (Box 33, Folder 38)
- No. 3995: Precarious Workers: Nail Technicians [Folder 3 of 4], 2011 (Box 33, Folder 39)
- No. 3995: Precarious Workers: Nail Technicians [Folder 4 of 4], 2011 (Box 33, Folder 40)
- Chautauqua Sewer District, 2011 (Box 33, Folder 41)
  WNYCOSH, #3996, 5/24/11
- Chautauqua Sewer District, 2011 (Box 33, Folder 42)
  WNYCOSH, #3997, 6/21/11
- Tech. Asst., 2011 (Box 33, Folder 43)
  MCWA, #3998, 2/10/11
- Tech. Asst., 2011 (Box 33, Folder 44)
  All-Treat Farm, #3999, 4/13/11
- Tech. Asst., 2011 (Box 33, Folder 45)
  Willsky, #4001, 4/19/11
- Worker's Compensation Project (Proposed), 2011 (Box 33, Folder 46)
  Cornell-ILR/Labor, #4002
- Lead Training (Proposal), 2011 (Box 33, Folder 47)
  Broome County, #4003
- Cayuga County Coop Ext.- Firefighters, 2011 (Box 33, Folder 48)
  WNYCOSH, #4004, 11/12/11
- Code Rule 59, 2010 (Box 33, Folder 49)
  NYS W.C., #4005
- Roadkill, 2012 (Box 33, Folder 50)
  USCC, #4006, 1/19/12
- Health and Safety of Composting, 2012 (Box 33, Folder 51)
  USCC, #4007, 1/17/12
- When Bad Things Happen, 2012 (Box 33, Folder 52)
  USCC, #4008, 1/17/12
- Mold, 2011 (Box 33, Folder 53)
  WNYCOSH, #4009, 6/14/11
- Chemical Hazards, 2011 (Box 33, Folder 54)
  WNYCOSH, #4010, 6/14/11
- MRB Inc.- Mold, 2011 (Box 33, Folder 55)
  WNYCOSH, #4011, 7/25/11
- MRB Inc., Chemical Safety, 2011 (Box 33, Folder 56)
  WNYCOSH, #4012, 7/25/11
- MCWA, 2011 (Box 33, Folder 57)
  WNYCOSH, #4013, 7/26/11
- Office Hazcom for MCWA, 2011 (Box 33, Folder 58)
  WNYCOSH, #4014, 7/26/11
- USEPA- Integrated Pest Mgmt. (Proposed), 2011 (Box 33, Folder 59)
  WNYCOSH, #4015
- Green and Healthy Homes- National, 2012 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  #4016
- Onondaga County- JHA, 2011 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  WNYCOSH, #4017, 7/5/11
- Onondaga County- Process Failure Analysis, 2011 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  WNYCOSH, #4018, 7/27/11
- Office Ergonomics- Deaf Services, 2011 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  WNYCOSH, #4019, 7/29/11
- Office Hazcom- MCWA, 2011 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  WNYCOSH, #4020, 7/26/11
- Beauty Salon Sensor- NIOSH/SBIR (Proposed), 2011 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  Synkera Tech., #4021, 8/5/11
- Article for Clearwaters, 2011 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  NYWEA, #4022, 9/2011
- Training Skills, 2011 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  WNYCOSH, #4023, 9/22/11
- Workers Rights, 2011 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  WNYCOSH, #4024, 9/12/11
- Tech. Asst., 2011 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  AmeriCorps, #4025, 7/6/11
- Interview- Coking, 2011 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  Center for Public Integrity, #4026
- NYWEA, 2012 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  WNYCOSH, #4027, 4/19/12
- NYWEA, 2012 (Box 34, Folder 13)
  WNYCOSH, #4028, 3/15/12
- NYWEA, 2012 (Box 34, Folder 14)
  WNYCOSH, #4029, 6/20/12
- Statistical Practice, 2011 (Box 34, Folder 15)
  Cornell-ILR, #4030, 11/7/11
- Occupational Epidemic, 2011 (Box 34, Folder 16)
  Cornell-ILR, #4031, 11/7/11
- No. 4032: Bureau Veritas [Folder 1 of 2], 2011 (Box 34, Folder 17)
- No. 4032: Bureau Veritas [Folder 2 of 2], 2011 (Box 34, Folder 18)
- Buffalo Schools, 2011 (Box 34, Folder 19)
  WNYCOSH, #4033, 10/17/11
- Buffalo Schools, 2011 (Box 34, Folder 20)
  WNYCOSH, #4034, 10/18/11
- Buffalo Schools, 2011 (Box 34, Folder 21)
  WNYCOSH, #4035, 10/19/11
- Buffalo Schools, 2011 (Box 34, Folder 22)
  WNYCOSH, #4036, 10/20/11
- Buffalo Schools, 2011 (Box 34, Folder 23)
  WNYCOSH, #4037, 10/21/11
- Buffalo Schools, 2011 (Box 34, Folder 24)
  WNYCOSH, #4038, 10/24/11
- Buffalo Schools, 2011 (Box 34, Folder 25)
  WNYCOSH, #4039, 10/25/11
- Buffalo Schools, 2011 (Box 34, Folder 26)
  WNYCOSH, #4040, 10/25/11
- Buffalo Schools, 2011 (Box 34, Folder 27)
  WNYCOSH, #4041, 10/26/11
- Buffalo Schools, 2011 (Box 34, Folder 28)
  WNYCOSH, #4042, 10/27/11
- Buffalo Schools, 2011 (Box 34, Folder 29)
  WNYCOSH, #4043, 10/27/11
- Buffalo Schools, 2011 (Box 34, Folder 30)
  WNYCOSH, #4044, 10/28/11
- Cosmetology Hazards, 2011 (Box 34, Folder 31)
  WNYCOSH, #4045, 11/14/11
- United Way-Ergonomics, 2011 (Box 34, Folder 32)
  WNYCOSH, #4046, 10/12/11
- Safety and Health- Composting, 2012 (Box 34, Folder 33)
  WNYCOSH, #4047, 8/3/12
- #4048 (Box 34, Folder 34)
- Cornell Sustainability (Proposal), 2012 (Box 34, Folder 35)
  #4049
- Manual- JHA- Disabilities, 2011 (Box 34, Folder 36)
  EDI: Safety and Health and Disabilities, #4050
- Ergonomics, 2011 (Box 34, Folder 37)
  WNYCOSH, #4051, 9/19/11
- Worker Rights, 2012 (Box 34, Folder 38)
  WNYCOSH, #4052, 2/6/12
- Tech. Asst.- Industrial Foods Fire, 2011 (Box 34, Folder 39)
  Bryant Simon, #4053, 9/1/11
- Conference (Proposed), 2012 (Box 34, Folder 40)
  NYWEA, #4054, 2/2012
- Tech. Asst., 2011 (Box 34, Folder 41)
  Millman, Inc., #4055, 9/13/11
- Worker Rights, 2011 (Box 34, Folder 42)
  WNYCOSH, #4056, 9/19/11
- Hazcom, 2011 (Box 34, Folder 43)
  WNYCOSH, #4057, 9/20/11
- Ergonomics, 2011 (Box 34, Folder 44)
  WNYCOSH, #4058, 9/20/11
- United Way- Ergonomics, 2011 (Box 34, Folder 45)
  WNYCOSH, #4059, 11/15/11
- Tech. Asst.- Fire Scenario, 2011 (Box 34, Folder 46)
  University of TX, #4060, 9/13/11
- Toxics Use Reduction (Proposed), 2011 (Box 34, Folder 47)
  WNYCOSH, #4061
- Tech. Asst.- Histoplasmosis etal., 2011 (Box 34, Folder 48)
  MCWA, #4062, 9/20/11
- Tech Asst., 2011 (Box 34, Folder 49)
  MCWA, #4062, 9/18/11
- Accident Investigation, 2012 (Box 34, Folder 50)
  WNYCOSH, #4063, 1/24/12
- Accident Investigation, 2012 (Box 34, Folder 51)
  WNYCOSH, #4064, 1/26/12
- Crisis Management, 2011 (Box 34, Folder 52)
  WNYCOSH, #4065, 11/2/11
- Crisis Management, 2011 (Box 34, Folder 53)
  WNYCOSH, #4066, 11/2/11
- Crisis Management, 2011 (Box 34, Folder 54)
  WNYCOSH, #4067, 11/3/11
- Crisis Management, 2011 (Box 34, Folder 55)
  WNYCOSH, #4068, 11/3/11
- JHA- Bureau Veritas, 2012 (Box 34, Folder 56)
  WNYCOSH, #4069, 6/18/12
- Tech. Asst., 2011 (Box 34, Folder 57)
  MCWA, #4070, 10/06/11
- Hazmat Refresher [Folders 1-5], 2012 (Box 34, Folder 58)
  IUOE, #4071-4075, 2/9-27/12
- Hazmat Initial, 2012 (Box 34, Folder 59)
  IUOE, #4076, 2/14/12
- Hazmat Initial, 2012 (Box 34, Folder 60)
  IUOE, #4077, 2/15/12
- Lead Renovator- Initial, 2012 (Box 34, Folder 61)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 11C#4078, 1/5/12, Wheaton
- Tech. Asst., 2011 (Box 34, Folder 62)
  Willett Dairy, #4079, 10/24/11
- Tech. Asst., 2011 (Box 34, Folder 63)
  Flaherty and Shea, #4080, 12/13/11
- #4081 (Proposed), 2011 (Box 34, Folder 64)
- Disaster Site Worker, 2012 (Box 34, Folder 65)
  IUOE, #4082, 2/22/12
- BioCycle, 2011 (Box 34, Folder 66)
  #4083; Contains Nov. issue of BioCycle
- Vulnerable Workers- Noise/Thermal Stress, 2011 (Box 34, Folder 67)
  WNYCOSH, #4084, 12/16/11
- Work, Health, Health Care, 2012 (Box 34, Folder 68)
  Cornell Resident, #4085, 2/7/12
- Tech. Asst., 2011 (Box 34, Folder 69)
  Patterson's Farm, #4086, 11/17/11
- Asphalt Highway Paving, 2012 (Box 34, Folder 70)
  WNYCOSH, #4087, 3/21/12
- United Way- Ergonomics, 2011 (Box 34, Folder 71)
  WNYCOSH, #4088, 12/7/11
- Site Evaluation, 2011 (Box 34, Folder 72)
  Tompkins County Library, #4089, 12/15/11
- Module of OSHA 30 Hour Course, 2012 (Box 34, Folder 73)
  IUOE, #4090, 3/13/12
- Xylem Accident Investigation, 2012 (Box 34, Folder 74)
  WNYCOSH, #4091, 1/31/12
- Xylem- Lockout/Tagout, 2012 (Box 34, Folder 75)
  WNYCOSH, #4092, 3/2/12
- Xylem- Blood Borne Pathogens, 2012 (Box 34, Folder 76)
  WNYCOSH, #4093, 3/8/12
- Xylem- Blood Borne Pathogens, 2012 (Box 34, Folder 77)
  WNYCOSH, #4094, 3/8/12
- Xylem- Blood Borne Pathogens, 2012 (Box 34, Folder 78)
  WNYCOSH, #4095, 3/8/12
- Xylem- Blood Borne Pathogens, 2012 (Box 34, Folder 79)
  WNYCOSH, #4096, 3/8/12
- Xylem- Blood Borne Pathogens, 2012 (Box 34, Folder 80)
  WNYCOSH, #4097, 3/8/12
- Xylem- Risk Mapping, 2012 (Box 34, Folder 81)
  WNYCOSH, #4098, 3/16/12
- Xylem- Aging, 2012 (Box 34, Folder 82)
  WNYCOSH, #4099, 4/4/12
- Xylem- Aging, 2012 (Box 34, Folder 83)
  WNYCOSH, #4100, 4/4/12
- Xylem- Aging, 2012 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  WNYCOSH, #4101, 4/4/12
- Xylem- Aging, 2012 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  WNYCOSH, #4102, 4/4/12
- Xylem- Aging, 2012 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  WNYCOSH, #4103, 4/4/12
- Interview, 2011 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  Waste and Recycling News, #4104, 12/5/11
- Tech. Asst., 2011 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  Homeowner, #4105, 12/6/11
- Tech. Asst., 2011 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  Tifft Nature Preserve, #4106, 11/29/11
- Lead Renovator- Initial, 2012 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 11C#4107, 2/7/12, Wheaton
- Lead Renovator- Initial, 2012 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 11C#4108, 2/28/12, Wheaton
- Lead Renovator- Initial, 2012 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 11C#4109, 3/6/12, Wheaton
- Lead Renovator- Initial, 2012 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 11C#4110, 3/20/12, Wheaton
- Lead Renovator- Initial, 2012 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 12C#4111, 4/4/12, Wheaton
- Lead Renovator- Initial, 2012 (Box 35, Folder 12)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 12C#4112, 4/20/12, Wheaton
- Lead Renovator- Initial, 2012 (Box 35, Folder 13)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 12C#4113, 5/1/12, Wheaton
- Lead Renovator- Initial, 2012 (Box 35, Folder 14)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 12C#4114, 5/15/12, Wheaton
- Lead Renovator- Initial, 2012 (Box 35, Folder 15)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 12C#4115, 6/5/12, Wheaton
- Lead Renovator- Initial, 2012 (Box 35, Folder 16)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 11C#4116, 6/12/12, Wheaton
- Lead Renovator- Initial, 2012 (Box 35, Folder 17)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 11C#4117, 7/19/12, Wheaton
- Lead Renovator- Initial, 2012 (Box 35, Folder 18)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 11C#4118, 7/30/12, Wheaton
- Lead Renovator- Initial, 2012 (Box 35, Folder 19)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 11C#4119, 8/14/12, Wheaton
- Lead Renovator- Initial, 2012 (Box 35, Folder 20)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 11C#4120, 8/21/12, Wheaton
- Lead Renovator- Initial, 2012 (Box 35, Folder 21)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 11C#4121, 9/11/12, Wheaton
- Lead Renovator- Initial, 2012 (Box 35, Folder 22)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 11C#4122, 9/26/12, Wheaton
- Lead Renovator- Initial, 2012 (Box 35, Folder 23)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 11C#4123, 10/2/12, Wheaton
- Lead Renovator- Initial, 2012 (Box 35, Folder 24)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 11C#4124, 10/16/12, Wheaton
- Lead Renovator- Initial, 2012 (Box 35, Folder 25)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 11C#4125, 11/6/12, Wheaton
- Lead Renovator- Initial, 2012 (Box 35, Folder 26)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 11C#4126, 11/13/12, Wheaton
- Lead Renovator- Initial, 2012 (Box 35, Folder 27)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 11C#4127, 12/4/12, Wheaton
- Lead Renovator- Initial, 2012 (Box 35, Folder 28)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, 11C#4128, 12/11/12, Wheaton
- Training Skills, 2012 (Box 35, Folder 29)
  WNYCOSH, #4129, 7/24/12
- Tech. Asst., 2011 (Box 35, Folder 30)
  Hardie Farm, #4131, 11/28/11
- Lewiston WWTP- Biohazards, 2012 (Box 35, Folder 31)
  WNYCOSH, #4132
- Article, 2011-2012 (Box 35, Folder 32)
  BioCycle, #4133, 12/16/11; Contains January 2012 issue of BioCycle
- Digester Training, 2012 (Box 35, Folder 33)
  Cornell Dairy, #4134, 6/27/12
- Digester Training, 2012 (Box 35, Folder 34)
  Cornell Dairy, #4135, 10/25/12
- Digester Training, 2012 (Box 35, Folder 35)
  Cornell Dairy, #4136, 11/8/12
- Digester Training, 2012 (Box 35, Folder 36)
  Cornell Dairy, #4137, 12/7/12
- Confined Space, 2012 (Box 35, Folder 37)
  Onondaga County, #4140, 2/8/12
- Confined Space, 2012 (Box 35, Folder 38)
  Onondaga County, #4141, 2/23/12
- Asphalt Highway Paving, 2012 (Box 35, Folder 39)
  WNYCOSH, #4142, 1/10/12
- Crisis Management, 2012 (Box 35, Folder 40)
  WNYCOSH, #4143, 5/10/12
- Workplace Violence, 2012 (Box 35, Folder 41)
  WNYCOSH, #4144, 6/28/12
- Vulnerable Workers, 2012 (Box 35, Folder 42)
  WNYCOSH, #4146, 9/19/12
- Workers' Rights- OSHA, 2012 (Box 35, Folder 43)